(Howard:)not trying to get to the bottom
of a dog-walking scam.
Oh, stop!
(Bernadette:)You know what's
really happening?
(Bernadette:)All the movies
you've watched,
(Bernadette:)the TV shows, the comic books...
(Bernadette:)they've completely twisted
your thinking.
(Bernadette:)No one's after you,
no one's listening to you,
(Bernadette:)no one cares about you.
(Raj:)I'd like to think
the "Four on Your Side" guy
cares about me.
(Penny:)You know, Beverly,
I know you and Alfred
(Penny:)have your differences,
but if you think about it,
(Penny:)if you hadn't married him,
there'd be no Leonard.
(chuckles)
(Penny:)So that's good, right?
Eh.
(Leonard:)Is that Howard
in front of us?
(Penny:)Oh, maybe.
(Penny:)Get closer.
(Howard:)Oh, God.
(Howard:)I think someone's
following us.
(Bernadette:)You're being ridiculous.
(Howard:)I'm not being ridiculous...
he's right on my tail.